shopcoogi.com 2019-06-14

# Privacy Policy - Coogi

COOGI DIGITAL PRIVACY AND SECURITY POLICY

COOGI is committed to your privacy

Your privacy is important to us at COOGI, so we have created the following Privacy and Security Policy to let you know what information we collect when you visit our web site, www.coogi.com, why we collect it, and how it is used. This Privacy and Security Policy also addresses our data security practices, the options you have to access and control any personally identifiable information you provide to us, and other matters. This Privacy and Security Policy is governed by our Terms and Conditions. We may periodically make changes to this Privacy and Security Policy which will be included on this page. It is your responsibility to review this Privacy and Security Policy frequently and remain informed about any changes to it, so we encourage you to visit this page often. By purchasing our products or using our services or website, you consent to the collection, use and disclosure of your personal information in accordance with the following privacy policy.

Information We Collect

We receive and may keep information voluntarily given to us when you decided to make a COOGI purchase, register on a COOGI website, take part in a special promotion, or provide any other information or unique preferences to better serve you. This information may include your name, address and phone number; date of birth; your e-mail address; your credit card information; proof of your identity; other ‘real world’ contact information and, such other information that COOGI may voluntarily collect from you from time to time on its website or through alternate means. It might also include information you provide us about other people. For example, you may provide us with some of the same information as above (name and address) for a merchandise gift recipient. When you provide us with personal information about the intended recipient of a shipment, we use that information for the purposes of processing the shipment and, in some cases, to communicate with the intended recipient to provide information pertaining to the status of the shipment. We rely on you to obtain the intended recipient’s consent to our use of their personal information for these limited purposes. We may receive information about you from other sources such as updated address information. This information may help us to improve our ability to serve your needs such as ensuring the accurate delivery of direct mail materials.

Use of Cookies and Other Technology

We want you to be aware that certain online tools exist to help us serve and recognize you when you visit our website. For your convenience, to help us personalize your experience or better serve your needs, we may receive and store certain types of information when you visit our website. You may be familiar with the term “cookies.” These cookies may be placed on your computer when you click on a COOGI e-mail, banner, or on the site directly. Cookies are very tiny text files that are stored on your computer when you visit certain web pages that record your preferences. COOGI uses cookies to keep track of what you have in your shopping cart and to remember you when you return to our store. We use this information to understand how users navigate to and around our websites, view product pages, access content and make purchases. You must accept cookies to shop at COOGI.

We may use third-party advertising companies to serve ads on our behalf

These companies may employ cookies and action tags (also known as single pixel gifs or web beacons) to measure advertising effectiveness.

Once Information Is Received, How Is It Used and/or Shared?

Information we collect from you may be shared between all points of contact within COOGI and its affiliates and subsidiaries. We use this information to offer you special offers, new products, and services and may share your information with affiliated and unaffiliated companies, sponsors and other third parties in COOGI’s sole and exclusive discretion. In addition, COOGI may use such information to provide you with timely and reliable fulfillment of requests; do all things necessary to administer those services; deliver merchandise and services that you purchase online; register you on COOGI.com; facilitate payment for your purchases; confirm your orders and delivery information; respond to your customer service inquiries or requests; communicate offers, benefits and featured items to you; administer giveaways, contests, and similar promotions; administer special customer recognition programs; find and stock the products you want; customize your shopping experience and other uses as determined by COOGI; analyze and support your purchases from COOGI; and analyze your use of the COOGI.com web site.

Certain business services are performed on COOGI’s behalf and at COOGI’s request by third parties and other companies. We may share your information with selected vendors that perform services for COOGI or to others for other marketing purposes. To perform these services, these companies may, at times, utilize some of the information you have provided COOGI. This information is used for the purposes COOGI has requested such as maintaining our database, administering and monitoring e-mails, and contest administration.

We may also share information with governmental agencies or other companies assisting us in fraud prevention or investigation. We may do so when (1) permitted or required by law, or (2) trying to protect against or prevent actual or potential fraud or unauthorized transactions, or (3) investigating fraud that has already taken place. In addition, COOGI reserves the right to disclose personal information to a third party if a law, regulation, search warrant, subpoena or court order legally requires or authorizes us to do so.

Retention of Personal Information

COOGI generally keeps user data on our server or in our archives for as long as we reasonably need it. We may alter this practice according to changing requirements. For example, we may delete some data if needed to free up storage space. We may keep other data for longer periods if the law requires it. In addition, information posted in a public forum could stay in the public domain indefinitely. Your consent to such purposes(s) remains valid after any termination of our relationship with you.

Right to Transfer

COOGI also reserves the right to disclose and/or transfer personal information to a third party in the event of a proposed or actual purchase, sale (including, but not limited to, liquidation, bankruptcy, realization, foreclosure or repossession), lease, license, merger, amalgamation or any other type of acquisition, disposal, transfer, conveyance or financing of all or any portion of COOGI or of any of the business, assets, interests or shares of COOGI or any divisions thereof. COOGI further reserves the right to sell, license, lease, share, transfer or otherwise disclose personal information to third parties at COOGI’s sole discretion. COOGI may decide to retain a copy of the information after the sale or transfer for any use.

Third party sites

COOGI may contain links to third party websites, including sites of providers that post last-minute content on this Site. COOGI is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites. Your use of these third party websites is entirely at your own risk. When you click on a link, you are essentially taken to the originating provider’s site.

Our Commitment to Data Security

COOGI makes commercially reasonable efforts to ensure that personal information collected from you is protected against loss and unauthorized access. This protection applies in relation to information stored in both electronic and hard copy form. COOGI uses industry standard security techniques on its website to help protect against the loss, misuse or modification of information that you have provided. When you access your personal information or transmit personally identifiable data to us, that information is stored on servers that we have used commercially reasonable efforts to protect from unauthorized access or intrusion. While we implement the above security measures, you should be aware that 100% security is not possible.

If You Have a Privacy Question

If you have a privacy question about the COOGI web site, please email: Customer Service at info@coogi.com. Or write:

COOGI  
350 Fifth Ave  
Suite 6540  
New York, New York 10118

California Privacy Rights

This supplements the Privacy and Security Policy above.

Beginning January 1, 2005, under California’s “Shine the Light” law, California residents who provide personal information in obtaining products or services for personal, family or household use are entitled to request and obtain from us once a calendar year information about the customer information we shared, if any, with other businesses for their own direct marketing uses. If applicable, this information would include the categories of customer information and the names and addresses of those businesses with which we shared customer information for the immediately prior calendar year (e.g., requests made in 2015 will receive information regarding 2014 sharing activities).

To obtain this information, please send an e-mail message to info@coogi.com with “Request for California Privacy Information” on the subject line and in the body of your message. We will provide the requested information to you at your e-mail address in response. Please be aware that not all information sharing is covered by the “Shine the Light” requirements and only information on covered sharing will be included in our response.
